In this course, I have learned about version control using Git and GitHub. I learned how to fork repositories, make changes locally, commit those changes, and create pull requests. The most important skills I gained include cloning repositories to my local machine, editing files, using git add and git commit commands, and pushing changes back to GitHub. This collaborative workflow is essential for software development and open source contribution.
